[{
    "question": "`5+1`",
    "answer": "`6`"
},
{
    "question": "`6+3`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+1`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`9+2`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`4+3`",
    "answer": "`7`"
},
{
    "question": "`5+5`",
    "answer": "`10`"
},
{
    "question": "`6+2`",
    "answer": "`8`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+3`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`5+4`",
    "answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+2`",
    "answer": "`10`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+3`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`6+5`",
    "answer": "`11`"
},
{
    "question": "`7+3`",
    "answer": "`10`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+5`",
    "answer": "`15`"
},
{
    "question": "`9+4`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+5`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`6+6`",
    "answer": "`12`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+6`",
    "answer": "`16`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+7`",
    "answer": "`15`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+4`",
    "answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`9+7`",
    "answer": "`16`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+8`",
    "answer": "`16`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+4`",
    "answer": "`14`"
},
{
    "question": "`12+4`",
    "answer": "`16`"
}, {
    "question": "`13+2`",
    "answer": "`15`"
},
{
    "question": "`15+4`",
    "answer": "`19`"
},
{
    "question": "`12+10`",
    "answer": "`22`"
},
{
    "question": "`14+3`",
    "answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`15+5`",
    "answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`16+7`",
    "answer": "`23`"
},
{
    "question": "`19+2`",
    "answer": "`21`"
},
{
    "question": "`20+3`",
    "answer": "`23`"
},
{
    "question": "`15+4`",
    "answer": "`19`"
},
{
    "question": "`10+7`",
    "answer": "`17`"
},
{
    "question": "`16+4`",
    "answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`19+6`",
    "answer": "`25`"
},
{
    "question": "`17+4`",
    "answer": "`21`"
},
{
    "question": "`16+2`",
    "answer": "`18`"
},
{
    "question": "`18+4`",
    "answer": "`22`"
},
{
    "question": "`15+7`",
    "answer": "`22`"
},
{
    "question": "`8+5`",
    "answer": "`13`"
},
{
    "question": "`18+5`",
    "answer": "`23`"
},
{
    "question": "`19+13`",
    "answer": "`32`"
},
{
    "question": "`17+9`",
    "answer": "`26`"
},
{
    "question": "`18+7`",
    "answer": "`25`"
},
{
    "question": "`17+5`",
    "answer": "`22`"
},
{
    "question": "`14+8`",
    "answer": "`22`"
},
{
    "question": "`7+2`",
    "answer": "`9`"
}]